ziki.com 2006-12-30

# Ziki.com : Be visible

### 1\. OUR COMMITMENT TO ONLINE PRIVACY

Your privacy is extremely important to Ziki. Please take a minute to read the following Privacy Policy so that you understand our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information relating to your use of the Ziki.com Site and Service (“Ziki.com” and “Service”), and the choices you can make about how your information is collected and used. As we update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms of Use, which governs your use of the Service in general. By visiting Ziki.com, providing personal information, and/or using the Service, you (“User”) signify your agreement to all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to all these terms and conditions, please do not provide us with any information and do not use Ziki.com.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Ziki.com does not own or control, or to people that Ziki.com does not employ or manage.

If you have any questions or concerns about Ziki.com’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@ziki.com](mailto:privacy@ziki.com)

### 2\. OUR COLLECTION AND USE OF ZIKI.COM USER INFORMATION

#### Collection of information

  1. We collect user-submitted personal information, including name, e-mail address, and birthdate, in order to verify new accounts and send notifications regarding the Service. We also collect additional data that is included in each User’s profiles, including without limitation: occupation, interests, gender and location as well as various other data that may change from time to time . This additional data may be available to other Users and/or the general public for viewing. 
  2. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, including IP address and browser type. 
  3. We do not collect or maintain information on the Service from Users whom we actually know to be under 13 years of age, and no part of our Service is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### Use of personally identifiable information submitted to Ziki

  1. To facilitate the Service, Ziki.com displays to other Users and visitors some of the personal information that we request. Ziki.com displays User profile information, profile photo, and username, to enable us to personalize a Users’ Ziki.com experience and to enable them to invite new friends and locate other Users with similar interests. Your e-mail address will never be displayed to other Users unless you specifically provide this information in your “Contact” section. However, we use your e-mail address to send notifications relating to Ziki.com.
  2. To promote your Ziki Profile, and thereby Ziki.com, we may sometimes run adword campaigns (listing your Ziki at the top of web search results for Google, Yahoo, MSN and others) by buying your first name and/or last name (provided to us when you registered). If you do not want us to do so, please email us at [contact@ziki.com](mailto:contact@ziki.com) .

#### Use of non-personally identifiable information

We use your IP address and browser type for the general administration of Ziki.com.

#### Sharing of collected information with third parties

We do not sell, rent, share, trade, or give away any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission, in cases where you are expressly informed otherwise, or under the following circumstances:

  1. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  2. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud, situations involving potential physical threats to any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  3. We reserve the right to transfer information about you to a successor-in-interest that acquires the right to such information by acquiring the Service, acquiring Ziki.com or substantially all of Ziki.com’s assets, or merging with Ziki.com. In any of these events, Ziki.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### 3\. LINKS

Ziki.com contains links to other web sites. We recommend that, before leaving Ziki.com, you review our Privacy Policy: it only applies to information collected by us. We are not responsible for any other web sites, their respective privacy practices, or how they treat information about their users. We strongly suggest that you review their privacy policies to find out how they treat your personal information.

### 4\. USE OF COOKIES

We use “cookies” (small files placed on your hard drive) to manage sessions on the Service, remember your User preferences, and ensure that you do not continually see the same advertisements. Cookies must be enabled in order for you to use Ziki.com. Information stored in cookies is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

### 5\. COMMENTING OR POSTING ON ZIKI.COM

Please keep in mind that, whenever you decide to comment on, or post a tag, web site, or comment on Ziki.com, or you voluntarily disclose any personal information, any such information can be collected and used by other Ziki.com Users or visitors to Ziki.com, and you may receive unsolicited communications as a result.

### 6\. ACCESSING AND UPDATING INFORMATION

As a registered Ziki.com User, you can access your account information at any time by logging in to Ziki.com and clicking on the “My Account” page. There, you can correct, update, or remove your account information at any time.

### 7\. SECURITY

All User accounts are password-protected. We go to great lengths to protect the account information that you have provided us. Access to this information is limited to only the Ziki employees who need it in order to perform their job function, such as customer service representatives. However, please note that we do not guarantee account security. Hardware or software failure, unauthorized use, and other factors may lead to a security breach. If you have any questions about this, please contact us at [privacy@ziki.com](mailto:privacy@ziki.com) .

### 8\. CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We will continuously assess our Privacy Policy against evolving technologies, business practices, and our Users ’ needs. As we diversify and update our Service, this Privacy Policy also may evolve. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at any time. If we do so, we will post the changes on Ziki.com so that our Users are aware of what information is collected, how that information is used, and under what circumstances, if any, the information is disclosed. Please check the Service periodically for Privacy Policy updates.

### 9\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions about your account, please contact Customer Service at [support@ziki.com](mailto:support@ziki.com) . If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact at [privacy@ziki.com](mailto:privacy@ziki.com) .
